Embrace:    Interact  Guide   Empower  Action
Innovate:   Engage    Invent  Distill  Connect 
Encourage:  Augment   Intent  Ethics   Reflect

good, beneficial, important, useful, beautiful, desirable and constructive

Respect, Friendship and Excellence

Friendship, patience, tolerance and love can be consider as social values. Honesty, creativity, imagination and excellence can be consider as personal values. Peace, human dignity, equal human rights and freedom can be consider as universal values. Respect to others and ourselves, keep promises, show gratitude to others, encourage others are moral values. Purity, piety, meditation, self-discipline, self-control, devotion to god can be consider as spiritual values. 

Health is the greatest gift,
Contentment is the greatest wealth,
Trust is the best relative,
Liberated mind is the greatest bliss.

Forgiveness
Optimism
Gratitude
Love
Honesty
Appreciation
.